

# Enikő Oros-Szebenyi dr. Frontend developer

The transition from medicine to technology was a big adventure, but at the same time, it was incredibly interesting. Proficient in front-end technologies and basics of server-side frameworks. I am motivated to join a group of seasoned and experienced developers.



🔷 enikoszebenyi@gmail.com



+3630/440 2728



1119 Budapest



<u>Website</u>



<u>LinkedIn</u>



GitHub

### Relevant projects

- In 2023 I've written clean, well-designed, and efficient web applications using the best software development practices.
- My projects are quality-assured by major tech institutions and companies.
- I created user-friendly web applications: Employee Manager, Registration App, Payment Details App
- Technologies used: JavaScript | TypeScript | RxJS | REST-API | ASP.NET Core | NodeJS-Express.js | SQL

### Core competencies

#### Problem-solving capability:

• The skills I learned in medical school, such as critical thinking, problem-solving, collaboration, and multitasking, were transferable in my new career.

#### **Self-motivation:**

• After finishing a basic Java course, I have the ability to motivate myself and keep on the path to constant learning and discovery.

### **Experience**

#### Angular developer

2023 - Present

#### Cubix Institute of Technology - online training center

- I developed a full-stack Angular application, where users could register/log in with their accounts and manage employees' data.
- Technologies used: Angular 13, Authentication, Router, MongoDB, Nodejs

#### JavaScript developer

2022 - 2023

#### Webuni - online training center

- One of my portfolio projects is a weather app where users can add capital cities to their list and see their current weather data.
- Made with Webpack, Web API-s, SCSS, Flexbox

#### Junior Java developer

2020 - 2021

#### A&K Academy - online training center

- I took part in multiple software development projects that they were organizing.
- I studied the concepts of algorithmic decomposition, database management, and the OOP principles.

#### Doctor of dental medicine

2014 - 2022

#### Private Health Companies

• I worked in private health sectors/startup companies during the last eight years. I collaborated with medical teams and took care of many satisfied patients. I am also employed in an international environment.

### Reference

,, She was always looking for opportunities to learn something new. She took part in multiple software development projects that we were organizing. It was a pleasure to teach her during the Java course.''

Andras Markos, Senior Software Engineer at Comrad Medical Systems

### Certifications

<ul> <li>Angular and TypeScript training (BMI-VIK certification)</li> </ul>	2023
<ul> <li>Advanced JavaScript course (CodeBerry)</li> </ul>	2023
<ul> <li>Modern JavaScript training (BMI-VIK certification)</li> </ul>	2022
Google IT Support (Coursera)	2022
• Junior Java Developer ( A&K Academy)	2020

### Education

2008-2014

• Semmelweis University

• Doctor of Dental medicine

## Languages

- Hungarian
- English
- Serbian